webmasterquest.com 2004-06-03

# Privacy Statement for WebmasterQuest

| 

|  | 

Privacy statement:  
  
---  

Why have a privacy statement?

**WebmasterQuest** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:   

Cookies

Our Site no longer uses cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We use a session ID that is sent with every request to the site. This ID expires after 20 minutes of inactivity.   

Use of personal information and email address

We will not sell your info to others. We use the personal info to get in touch with you when needed. We send out our site newsletter with updates and information about the site to keep you up with current developments. The newsletter is sent 1-4 times a month depending on how the site develops. When we release new features an email will be sent out.   

Registration Forms

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address). 

The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.   

External Links

This site contains links to other sites. **WebmasterQuest** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.   

Data Quality/Access

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send email to [ webmaster@webmasterquest.com ](mailto:webmaster@webmasterquest.com)
  2. You can visit the following URL: [ http://www.webmasterquest.com ](http://www.webmasterquest.com/)

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
